Guide to the Women's Studies Program records, 1981-2008 (bulk 1981-2002) UA.25.41.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Survey, 1987-1988; 6
  The materials in the Survey series of the Women's Studies Program records include responses from a 1987 survey created by WSP administrators and sent to women Duke graduates, as well as materials analyzing and summarizing the responses. The survey was sent to all women who received undergraduate degrees from Duke, as well as some who attended graduate school at Duke, from the 1920s through the 1980s, and surveys are organized by decade of graduation. The survey included questions about women's experiences as Duke students and activities since graduation as well as their views on the women's movement and major societal impacts on women's lives since the 1960s. The series includes more than 700 hand-written and typed responses. Also included are notes and analyses of the responses, primarily focusing on post-graduate education and career choices.
  - Tally information, 1988 (Box 19)
  - Enclosures from survey (all), 1988 (Box 19)
  - Data analysis materials, 1988 (Box 19)
  - Undergraduate Surveys: 1920s, 1987 (Box 20)
  - Undergraduate Surveys: 1930s, 1988 (Box 20)
  - Undergraduate Surveys: 1940s, 1987-1988 (Box 20)
  - Undergraduate Surveys: 1950s, 1987-1988 (Box 20)
  - Undergraduate Surveys: 1960s, 1987-1988; 2 folders (Box 20)
  - Undergraduate Surveys: 1970s, 1987-1988; 2 folders (Box 20)
  - Undergraduate Surveys: 1980s, 1987-1988; 2 folders (Box 20)
  - All graduate surveys, Undated (Box 20)